Christmas has never been so ruff.
Pups Alone is a family, comedy film directed by Alex Merkin.
After receiving an exciting new job opportunity at a cutting edge Pet Invention company, Robert, his teenage daughter Jenna and
their trusty and special border collie Charlie make the move to the new neighborhood, right before Christmas.
Upon arriving, Robert meets his gorgeous next door neighbor
Holly, and her sassy and spunky border collie Gidget.
Before the sparks can fly, they are set upon my Robert’s conniving and obnoxious next door neighbor and project
manager Victor, his neighborhood bully bulldog “Vinnie P” and the sycophantic sidekick Chihuahua “Jose”.
Charlie (voice), played by Jerry O'Connell.
Gidget (voice), played by Jennifer Love Hewitt.
Jose (voice), played by Rob Schneider.
Vinnie P (voice), played by Danny Trejo.
Oliver (voice), played by Malcolm McDowell.
The Wise Bartender, played by Keith David.
Pups Alone is a 2021 American Christmas slapstick comedy film written by Brandon Burrows and Jason Gruich, directed by Alex Merkin and starring
Dolph Lundgren and featuring the voices of Jerry O'Connell, Jennifer Love Hewitt, Rob Schneider, Danny Trejo and Malcolm McDowell.
The tone is lighthearted.